Contact

minhthu.tifa@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/minhthutifa (LinkedIn) right-slicer-c53.notion.site/ Portfolio-540b5a8b666e49b394aa713 (Portfolio) minhthutifa.wixsite.com/my-site (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Mobile Design
Userflows
Mobile Application Design

Certifications

Conduct UX Research and Test Early Concepts

Start the UX Design Process: Empathize, Define, and Ideate

Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design

Build Wireframes and Low-Fidelity Prototypes

Create High-Fidelity Designs and Prototypes in Figma

Minh Thu Nguyen

UI/UX designer | Full-Time Jobs Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Hi there, I'm Thu and I'm extremely passionate about the field of UI/UX design.

Having worked for both agencies and startups, I possess a great sense of aesthetics and design thinking, which enables me to create clean and user-friendly interfaces with a personal touch.

I have been awarded a Google UX Design Professional Certificate and have completed various design courses, including an Interactive UI/UX course taught by Gary Simon and a Complete Web Design Course taught by Vakoshvili on Skillshare, and so on.

I have experience in creating design systems, wireframes, user flows, prototypes, UI designs, conducting user research, usability studies, interviews and so on. My primary design tool is Figma, and I also use other tools like Photoshop and Illustrator to practice and further develop my design skills.

Visit my website: minhthutifa.wixsite.com/my-site Check out my Linkedin profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/minhthutifa/

Experience

Ven Agency - Digital Performance Agency UI/UX Designer
January 2023 - Present (2 years 3 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

I'm currently working full-time for Ven - an Australia agency. My roles included:

- Create intuitive and visually appealing interfaces for web and mobile applications that meet user needs and business requirements.
- Use design thinking to develop user flows, wireframes, prototypes, and final designs.

- Collaborate with developer team to ensure that designs are feasible and implemented correctly.
- Refine designs and improve the user experience based on client requirements.

Soundio

UI/UX Designer

August 2022 - November 2022 (4 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Soundio is a start-up company that owns a lot of new and exciting digital content including: audiobooks, podcasts, courses and more.

My role included:

- Create UI kit for web/app.
- Design, iterate, and validate product solution.
- The full spectrum of UI design from research and analysis, ideation, low fidelity, user flow, wireframes, high fidelity, prototypes, and iterative amends with the technical team to build the perfectly latest version.
- Collaborating effectively with product designer and technical team to enhance products.

Google

UX Designer

September 2021 - October 2021 (2 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Work on the Yumms App project. Yumms is a specialist food app designed to serve the type of users who have a passion for food. The app's unique feature is that users can customize their dishes if they so desire. I designed the mobile app from conception to deliverable while completing the Google UX design Professional Certificate Course. Throughout the project, I demonstrate my UX skills in conducting interviews, paper and digital wireframing, low and high-fidelity prototyping, conducting usability studies, accounting for accessibility, and iterating on designs.

Education

Skillshare

Web Designer Course, UI design · (May 2022)

Online DesignCourse - Gary Simon

Interactive UI/UX Course, UI/UX design · (June 2022 - September 2022)

Dai Hoc Thai Binh Duong

Bachelor's degree, Accounting · (October 2010 - October 2013)